你站的地方的右边会有个收银台
We'll make the deals on right at where you're standing.
那边会有个厨房
Oh, and over here, a gourmet kitchen.
还有  天花板上
And, and here from the ceiling,
会有一盏大大的水晶吊灯
a big all crystal chandelier here.
真不愧是你爸爸的女儿
You're your daddy's daughter, alright.
他以前也总是不停地唠叨这些
Used to go on and on about this old sugar mill too.
亲爱的
Petite cakes.
我相信这地方会焕然一新的
I'm sure this place is gonna be just wonderful.
但糟糕的是你会很辛苦
But it's a shame you're working so hard.
但我怎能在马上成功时半途而废呢
But how can I let up now when I am so close.
我得确保爸爸的艰辛
I've gotta make sure all daddy's
得到应有的回报
hard work means something.
蒂安娜  或许你爸爸没能得到
Tiana, your daddy may not have gotten the place
你梦想中的房子  但他拥有比这更好的
you always wanted but he had something better.